Utilizing cmake:
	*cmake is informed of everything we need to know, to generate .NET bindings
	*we can use the src/includes.cmake to get not just the header-files to wrap,
		- but also the order in which to wrap them
	*Wrapping tool can be called on each file, in order, using cmake list iteration
		- CppSharp has compile settings..., so we could compile the bindings via our tool,
			or just write a dumb generator and compile via cmake scripting
				> if cppsharp, we can use the settings from cmake, so it works as intended
				> if cmake only, we can still use the information in the tool
		- As the files are wrapped...
			- their wrapped counter-parts can be used as includes/usings in more advanced types as required
	*Follow the order indicated in the build, both for automated and manually wrapping this stupid thing.
	
C++ Templates:

	*C++/CLI supports templates AND run-time generics now, according to docs
	*Wrapper<TNativeType>?
		- need type marshalling
		- how to access methods/etc/things we dont know?
			> prolly through nesting templates, and template expansions, but uncertain
			> combined with a code generator perhaps this is the most effective?
